Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Podcasts and scripts, 2019 -- 2021; UA176.005049; 989 Megabytes; 24 Digital Object(s)
  - The Rewind, 2019 September -- 2021 April; UA176.005053; 373 Megabytes; 18 Digital Object(s)
    - Episode one: Tufts strikes for climate; swastika posted on door, 2019 September 30; UA176.005054; 21.48 Megabytes
      In the first-ever episode of The Rewind, Tufts students protest the complicity of Tufts and the state of Massachusetts in the climate crisis. A Jewish student finds a swastika affixed to their door, another incident of Antisemitism and white supremacy on the Tufts campus. Guests: Connor Dale and Austin Clementi.
    - Episode one script, 2019 September 30; UA176.005055; 8.98 Kilobytes
    - Episode three: student finds homophobic slur scratched into door, 2019 October 11; UA176.005056; 6.08 Megabytes
      Producer Tim Leong talks to reporter Alexander Thompson about the homophobic slur scratched into a Tufts student's door, marking the second incident of hate on campus this month.
    - Episode three script, 2019 October 11; UA176.005057; 8.18 Kilobytes
    - Episode four: African American exhibit defaced, bias response teams announced, 2019 October 18; UA176.005058; 18.17 Megabytes
      Producer Stephanie Rifkin speaks to reporter Robert Kaplan about the defacement of a sign in the African American Trail Project exhibit, and the subsequent creation of two Bias Response Teams.
    - Episode four script, 2019 October 18; UA176.005059; 8.94 Kilobytes
    - Episode five: Medford City Council requests Tufts' master plans, 2019 November 03; UA176.005060; 34.95 Megabytes
      Host Arlo Moore-Bloom talks to reporter Elie Levine about Medford's request for Tufts' institutional master plans, which would reveal future development plans for approximately the next ten years.
    - Episode six script, circa 2019 November; UA176.005061; 9.53 Kilobytes
    - Episode seven script, circa 2019 November; UA176.005062; 8.84 Kilobytes
    - Final episode: Tufts faculty donate overwhelmingly to Democrats, 2019 December 08; UA176.005063; 25.48 Megabytes
      Host Arlo Moore-Bloom talks to reporters Anton Shenk and Caleb Symons about their latest investigation on faculty donations to political organizations. Shenk and Symons found that ninety-four percent of donated money went to Democratic candidates and causes, while just under 1% went to Republican-aligned recipients.
    - Episode one: Tufts begins review of fossil fuel investment, 2020 February 18; UA176.005064; 17.1 Megabytes
      In this semester's first episode of The Rewind, host Leslie Gladstone interviews reporter Connor Dale and Tufts Climate Action representative Hanna Carr about the school's effort to review investments in its endowment.
    - The Rewind episode two script, circa 2020 February; UA176.005065; 8.83 Kilobytes
    - Episode 2: climate conversations: Tufts' ban on direct coal investments and winter weather trends, 2021 February 28; UA176.005066; 45.63 Megabytes
      On this episode of "The Rewind," we explore Tufts' Feb. 10 commitment to ban direct investment in coal and tar sands with Tufts Daily reporter Alicia Zou and Tufts Climate Action representative Grace Abe. We continue our climate discussion as The Rewind's Ty Blitstein talks with Daily reporters Katie Furey and Keira Myles about the winter weather. Stay tuned weekly for more stories from the Tufts Daily.
    - Episode 3: stories on the hill: equity and inclusion report, RA demands, and remote first-year experiences, 2021 March 07; UA176.005067; 39.21 Megabytes
      On today's episode, we talk with Michael Weiskopf, a news reporter at the Tufts Daily, about the recently released report from the university's Equity and Inclusion workstream, launched as part of its efforts to become an anti-racist institution. Additionally, Silvia Wang reports on residential assistants' demands for higher compensation and improved communication with the administration, and Nicole Garay speaks with remote first-year students about their Tufts experiences.
    - Episode 4: education on campus: Tufts applications, pedagogical partnership program, and Tisch College research, 2021 March 14; UA176.005068; 47.27 Megabytes
      On today's episode, we hear from Jack Maniaci about Tufts' early decision applications, and we share an update on the Pedagogical Partnership Program, which pairs students with faculty to promote equity and enhance academic experiences. We also dive further into education, discussing Tisch College's research on the state of civic education in Massachusetts and at the national level.
    - Episode 5: looking to the future: university vaccinations, recycling smart on campus, and pandemic study abroad, 2021 March 21; UA176.005069; 37.28 Megabytes
      On this Rewind episode, Governor Charlie Baker announced Wednesday that vaccines will be available to Massachusetts residents 16 and older on April 19; what does that mean for when and how Tufts students can be vaccinated? Also, we discuss a Green Fund project aimed at improving recycling habits on campus and how students are adjusting their plans to study abroad amid the pandemic.
    - Episode 6: supporting the community: spirituality, social justice, and Medford's finances, 2021 April 04; UA176.005070; 40.85 Megabytes
      On today's episode, Rewind Reporter Ty Blitstein shares his conversations with the University Chaplaincy about its deepening focus on social justice and its upcoming Russell Lecture on Spiritual Life. Delivering the lecture is Reverend Adam Russell Taylor, President of Sojourners, a nonprofit that aims to integrate faith with social justice. More on that later in today's episode. We also host a discussion with Jack Hirsch about the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on the City of Medford's finances.
    - Episode 7: tour of Campus: week's news, lights, and history of Tufts' buildings, 2021 April 11; UA176.005071; 39.95 Megabytes
      Tour of Campus: Week's news, lights, and history of Tufts' buildings by The Tufts Daily
  - Take Town, 2020 February -- 2020 October; UA176.005072; 616.15 Megabytes; 4 Digital Object(s)
    - Episode one: remembering Kobe, 2020 February; UA176.005073; 483.45 Megabytes
      In Episode 1 of Take Town, the only Tufts Daily sports podcast that matters or exists, Sam Weidner and Aiden Herrod discuss the storied legacy of Kobe Bryant — and its more complicated aspects.
    - Episode two: students, NFL: welcome back!, 2020 October; UA176.005074; 42.97 Megabytes
      Take Town is BACK for season 2! Aiden and Matt talk about the Fall return to sports, what this NFL season is going to look like, and explore what the heck this strange, strange time means for professional sports. Join us!
    - Episode three: the NBA finals, 2020 October; UA176.005075; 44.6 Megabytes
      Aiden and Matt break down the NBA Finals and other hardcourt matters.
    - Episode four: goat talk, 2020 October; UA176.005076; 45.13 Megabytes
      After another ring for Team Bron, Aiden and Matt are left with no other choice for this week's episode. That's right, Goat Talk. Also, a very special guest sits in. Join us!